<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fix A Flat</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="prestaText">Does the place where you put air in the tire look like this?</string>
    <string name="schraderText">Does the place where you put air in the tire look more like where you inflate a car\'s tire?</string>
    <string name="prestaButtonText">It looks like this.</string>
    <string name="schraderButtonText">It looks like a car\'s.</string>
    <string name="notThisValveButtonText">It doesn\'t look like this.</string>
    <string name="notices">
        This app assumes that you\'ve successfully removed your wheel and know how to replace it.
    </string>
    <string name="schraderTireRemoveStart">
        Deflate the tire completely: remove any cap on the small tube sticking out of the rim
        (where you put air into the tire, this is known as the stem) then push on the small pin
        in the center of the stem. If there is any air in the tire, you will hear it whoosing out
        of the tire.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="prestaTireRemoveStart">
        Deflate the tire completely: remove any cap on the small tube sticking out of the rim
        (where you put air into the tire, this is known as the stem) then unscrew the thumb bolt
        in the center of the stem completely. Now, push down on the pin in the center of the stem.
        If there is any air in the tire, you will hear it whoosing out of the tire.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="tireRemoveStart">
        Remove one side of the tire: Hook the rounded end of one tire lever under the bead
        (the outer edge) of the tire to unseat it. Hook the other end onto a spoke to hold the
        lever in place and to keep the unseated tire from popping back into the rim. Hook the
        rounded end of the second lever under the bead next to the first and walk it around the
        tire/rim clockwise until one side of the tire is off the rim.
    </string>
    <string name="prestaTubeRemove">
        To remove the tube, unscrew the ring nut at the bottom of the stem completely and set it
        aside. Then, push the stem through the hold in the rim and then carefully pull the tube
        out of the tire.
    </string>
    <string name="schraderTubeRemove">
        To remove the tube, push the stem through the hole in the rim and then carefully pull the
        tube out of the tire.
    </string>

    <string name="tireRemoveFinish">
        Remove the tire completely: Push the bead of other side of the tire completely off the
        rim.\n
        Inspect the tire to locate what caused the puncture in the first place.\n
        When you locate what caused the puncture, remove it from the tire or it will puncture the
        new tube when you inflate it.\n
        Once you\'ve located and removed the cause of the puncture, partially replace the tire on the rim by
        pushing one bead back on to the rim.\n
    </string>

    <string name="prestaTubeReplace">
        To replace the tube, partially inflate the tube. Push the stem through the hole in the rim,
        then screw the retenition ring nut back onto the stem so that it secures the stem to the rim.\n
        Gently push the tube into the tire.\n
    </string>

    <string name="schraderTubeReplace">
        To replace the tube, partially inflate the tube. Push the stem through the hole in the rim
        and gently push the tube into the tire.\n
    </string>

    <string name="finishTubeTireReplace">
        Once the tube is in place, install the second side of the tire:\n\n

        Starting at the valve on either side, push the second bead into the rim. This will become
        progressively harder as you push more and more of the bead into the rim.

        For the last few inches of tire bead, some considerable force may be needed to pop it over
        the edge of the rim. (Some rim/tire combinations are easier than others.) If it is giving
        you difficulty, resist the urge to press the middle part over. Instead, work alternately
        from each end of the section you\'re trying to lift over. Going back and forth from side
        to side will usually get it.
    </string>

    <string name="prestaInflateTire">
        Unscrew the pin at the center of the stem. Connect the pump to the stem and begin pumping.
        Once the tire is fully inflated, screw the pin at the center of stem closed.
    </string>

    <string name="schraderInflateTire">
        Connect the pump to the stem and begin pumping.
    </string>
</resources>
